

Contact



deblina4@gmail.com

Links







Skills

- JavaScript
- React
- Angular
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- HTML
- 227

Other Skills

- Customer Experience
- Quality Analysis
- Marketing & Advertising

Languages

- English
- Swedish
- Hindi
- Bengali

Deblina Mondal



Full-stack Developer/Front-end Developer

React | JavaScript | TypeScript | Node.js

A full-stack Developer with a passion for bringing ideas to life and creating content to simplify user experience. A driven professional with excellent communication skills which helps in interpreting and implementing client's vision. I thrive in environment that constantly embraces new technologies. I have done multiple projects in both frontend and backend.



Education

2 Years Diploma in Front-end Development (2020-2022) from Medieinstitutet



Employment history

2021 March - Till Date: Global IT Intern

- Developed a web app (React, Firebase) almost single handedly (70%).
- Following Agile methodology, leading the team of 5 developers.

2012 – 2020: Entrepreneurship (Apparels)

- Achieved an average growth of yearly 34%
- Able to give direct employment to 7 people and indirect to many more.

2010 - 2012: Teacher

- Teaching under=privileged children in association with a non-profit organization
- Increased the literacy rate to 17% of a particular area.

2008 - 2010: Process Leader - Customer care & Operations

- Managing a team of 20 associates
- Handling client escalations
- Analyzing data and applying strategies, increased customer satisfaction from 3.75 stars to 4.50 stars.

2007 - 2008: Customer Experience Specialist

- First point contact for people from sales, operations, and customers
- Handling customer escalations, achieved 0 escalations for 2 consecutive quarters.

2003 – 2007: Inbound Sales – Team Coach/Quality Analyst

- Analyzing data and applying strategies, achieved best performer award.
- Training associates on new products and promotions